Who says you can't fall in love every day?
Remember Sunday is a tv movie, romance, drama film directed by Jeff Bleckner.
A lonely, down-on-her-luck waitress meets a handsome, quirky jewelry
store clerk and thinks that maybe, finally, she's met Mr.
The more Molly gets to know Gus, the more she's intrigued by him.
But she's also mystified.
Gus is absent-minded, preoccupied.
Is he hiding something?
The short answer is: yes.
He's reluctant to share with her that since suffering a brain
aneurysm, he's totally lost his short-term memory.
Every day is a brand new day, his life starts anew.
Every day he sees Molly he struggles to remember
who she is and what she represents.
Every day, he has to fall in love with her all over again.
Molly, played by Alexis Bledel.
Gus, played by Zachary Levi.
Lucy, played by Merritt Wever.
Baptiste, played by Barry Shabaka Henley.
Jolene, played by Valerie Azlynn.
Jerry, played by David Hoffman.
Remember Sunday is a 2013 American romantic drama film directed by Jeff Bleckner, written by
Michael Kase and Barry Morrow, and starring Zachary Levi and Alexis Bledel.
The tone is emotional.